Hello everybody, this is DrewNailer. Today I'm going to show you how to install and configure
DSpellCheck in Notepad++. So if you haven't already, go ahead and open up Notepad++ and
we're going to go to Plugins, Admin, search for DSpellCheck, check the box next to it,
click install, click yes, and then type in your password and then click yes. It'll
install it. And now, as you can see, it's installed. If we try to type something,
it doesn't put the little squiggly line under it. So we need to go to Plugins,
DSpellCheck, Settings, change the library from Hunspell to Native Windows, and then
click OK. And even before I clicked OK, you can see that it changed it right there.
The reason why you would want to do this is Notepad++ seems to not have DSpellCheck
anymore. So I'm using version 7.9.2. I hope this video helped and please
let me know if you need any help with this in the comments below. Thank you for
watching and goodbye.